There’s a $2 trillion social welfare and climate package,
is what it’s being called.
Well, part of that is going to be about social welfare,
“human infrastructure,” as it’s being termed.
It might be paying people to stay home.
Does that upset an already fragile labor market right now,
where we have so many people not in the labor force?
Agriculture in particular, we really struggle because we pay so much
in that lower, unskilled labor pool.
And what if those people that are getting 20-plus-percent pay raises
get another 20% in 2022?
Or what if they don’t even show up?
That sign right there is from July.
I was on my way to Wisconsin to do a speaking engagement.
I pulled into Culver’s. You guys don’t have Culver’s out here.
Maybe you do. I don’t know.
I pulled in to get me a ButterBurger and to take a pee.
What’d that sign say?
“Due to being short-staffed, our dining room will be closed for the day.
Drive-through is open.”
You know how mad the Culver’s manager gets
when you pee in their drive-through?
Okay.